(Shine Brilliantly)
Nice to see you, everyone.
- Well... - Dae Ho. It's been a while.
I heard you guys did a good deed without me.
I enjoyed watching your episode at the end of the year.
It was heartwarming.
It's 2,330 dollars.
(Everyone wholeheartedly took part in the bazaar with goodwill.)
It's for a good cause.
(The collected donations reached a total of 24,015 dollars.)
(The sellers happily contributed to the donations as well.)
(Sung Hwan and Jae Hyeon joined in by making donations.)
In total,
we donated 52,000 dollars to the Community Chest of Korea.
- We raised a lot of money, right? - That's...
- Yes. - It's a plaque of appreciation.
Okay. Can you see?
We gladly took Kian84's recommendation into account...
- and decided to use the fund... - Yes.
to help disadvantaged senior citizens.
We'll get old too.
(That's right.)
- We'd like to thank everyone... - Right.
who made time during their busy day to come.
- We'll use it for a good cause. - Thank you.
Everyone participated out of compassion.
It's time to bring in the star of this week's Rainbow Live.
You know what year 2026 is, right?
Yes. It's the Year of the Red Horse.
It's the Year of the Red Horse.
(Galloping)
To celebrate 2026, the Year of the Red Horse,
we have a special project, Running Horses.
- The first star is... - The first horse.
He's horse number 1. "Weak Hero Class 2."
- "D.P. 2." - "D.P."
"Would You Marry Me."
He left an impression on the viewers with his acting in the dramas.
Now, he's actively performing in musicals.
Please welcome Bae Na Ra!
(Welcome to the show, Bae Na Ra.)
Welcome.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Nice to meet you. - Hello.
He's so handsome.
("Weak Hero Class 2")
(Once you see him act, you can't forget him.)
(He has grown into a lead actor in major dramas.)
("D.P. 2")
(He also became a scene stealer with a unique character.)
(He showed that no one could replace him as an actor.)
(A versatile actor with unexpected charms)
(Bae Na Ra)
- Hello. - Come to the middle.
- Hello. - My gosh.
- He's handsome. - Hello.
- Say hello to the viewers. - Thank you.
Hello.
I'm an actor. My name is Bae Na Ra.
- Nice to meet you. - All right.
It's your first time on our show. Can you tell us how it feels?
It really feels like I'm meeting celebrities now.
- I'm so nervous right now. - Really?
Yes. I'm over the moon.
I've always been so curious...
about how this studio looked in person.
Now, I got to see it in person.
You sound like a student on a field trip.
I really enjoy watching your show.
What do you have in common with horses?
Oh, that. I was born...
- In the Year of the Horse? - in the Year of the Horse.
(Connecting the dots)
- In the Year of the Horse. - Yes.
Here's our special project, Running Horses.
Let's check out the day-to-day life of our first star, Bae Na Ra.
(Let's check out the day-to-day life of Bae Na Ra.)
(The Year of the Red Horse)
(Rainbow Running Horses)
(I'm Happy to Be Me)
(Sleeping soundly)
(Na Ra is fast asleep, wrapped up in blankets.)
Watching my own clip feels so awkward.
- Don't you feel shy? - Right.
- It's your first time watching it. - Right.
(Opening his eyes)
(He wakes up at 9:30am.)
Gosh, look at my face.
(Shy)
Hello. I've been living alone for 16 years now.
I'm Actor Bae Na Ra. Nice to meet you all.
He's been living alone for a long time.
He's living alone.
You wore a mask to sleep.
I cover up my eyes, my ears,
and my mouth with a mask.
Why do you cover up your ears?
I don't like hearing noise. It gets loud in the morning.
Because of the noise, I got used to wearing earplugs.
So now, it feels weird not to wear them.
- I didn't know you could do that. - How long did it take...
for you to get used to that?
It took about three years.
Once you get used to this setup,
- Three years. - wherever you go,
it tricks your brain into thinking that you're in your bedroom.
- You cover up everything. - That's nice.
(Pulling back the curtain)
(Welcome to Na Ra's house.)
His room is clean.
It's a one-bedroom studio.
I've been living in this house for over six years.
Many good things happened while living here.
So I have a lot of good memories from this place.
I hang everything on the walls...
to use the space more efficiently.
(You can see hanging decor...)
(all over his house.)
Everyone has...
- Right. I hang everything. - their way of doing things.
(As long as he can hang them, the space turns into storage.)
That's neat.
(He makes good use of the walls.)
When you look around, you'll see I have everything I need,
neatly packed into this small space.
I've got everything I need.
So I don't have any useless items.
He lived there for six years, and his house looks so organized.
- Right. - Exactly.
He must be really good at keeping things organized.
(Strictly separating the areas)
I decorated the house the way I wanted.
I did everything I wanted to do in this house.
As you can see, the wall is completely gray.
- It's painted gray. - The wall has a different color.
I cut the curtains too.
As for the lights,
I used to have white lights.
But with my landlord's permission, I removed the lights...
and replaced them with LED lights.
That's a difficult job.
I had to detach them and get rid of them.
Looking at the door of the bathroom, I can see it's an old house.
That's right. I live in an old building.
- So I painted the door. - You painted it.
Wait. Did you do that yourself too?
It's a steel door, but I painted it.
- To make it look retro? - Yes.
You wanted the house to look older than it was?
It looks like a vacation home from ages ago.
Actually, it looks slightly better in person.
It reminds me of a cafe.
- Did the landlord see it? - When my landlord came to see it,
- my landlord was so happy. - Really?
- "You decorated the house well." - Really?
- It looks clean. - Right.
(Removing)
(He brushes his teeth as soon as he wakes up.)
(He makes the bed while brushing his teeth.)
I always make the bed when I wake up in the morning.
Following a routine...
brings positive energy. It's a promise I made to myself.
(He moves onto the next task while brushing his teeth.)
(He prepares the kettle to boil water.)
(As soon as he gets the kettle going,)
(he grabs the vacuum cleaner next to the kettle.)
(He keeps himself busy as soon as he wakes up.)
I live in a small studio.
So it gets dirty quickly.
(He quickly finishes cleaning while brushing his teeth.)
(He's multitasking to clean his room and brush his teeth.)
(He also cleans his throat.)
- He's so good at keeping it neat. - Right. He keeps things...
- so neatly. - He's using the small space well.
It's not easy to stack up the towels that neatly.
What's he doing?
The litter box?
(Diligently digging up potatoes)
- There it is. - I have a cat...
named Gureum.
An actor friend of mine was looking after Gureum temporarily...
- until someone adopted Gureum. - What a beautiful cat.
- How cute. - Yes.
My Gureum is friendly like a puppy.
- Gureum is a gentle cat. - My goodness.
- Gureum is the kindest. - What a gentle cat.
- What a gentle cat. - Gureum is always with me.
Gureum is my precious family.
I took Gureum's behaviors into consideration...
and set up the cat tower on my own.
So Gureum can move around the house.
- I really love the color. - What a beautiful cat.
(He quickly finishes removing poop from the litter box.)
You're off to a diligent morning.
- Your morning... - It's going smoothly.
- Everything looks so natural. - Right.
I don't like getting lazy in the morning.
(He naturally pours the boiled water into the cup.)
(Adding the health supplement)
- You're following your own routine. - Right.
You know what I noticed?
He's really good at putting things back...
- in their places - That's right.
- Yin-Yang Water. - Yes.
You mix cold and hot water...
- to make that, right? - Yes. That's right.
(He quickly washes the cup and puts it back.)
- He does it right away. - Right away.
(Opening the fridge right away)
(The items in the fridge are aligned perfectly.)
Look at the alignment.
(Neat)
(Let me have some eggs.)
(He fills the bowl with boiled water.)
What?
(Is he washing the eggs?)
- I use lukewarm water... - You're washing them?
to warm up the cold eggs.
- In case they crack in hot water? - Yes.
- So I washed them. Yes. - That's why you did that?
I put the eggs in hot water.
- What? - What?
Siri.
Set an eight-minute timer.
(He goes back to the fridge after setting an 8-minute timer.)
(Filling the glass with tomato juice)
- What's that? - Calamansi.
- Don't people add that to liquor? - Right.
- He's adding another ingredient. - Olive oil?
That's my recipe.
That looks good, though.
- He's adding an ingredient again. - It's a healthy recipe.
- Another ingredient? - My gosh.
(Adding black pepper)
(Gulping down)
That must hit the spot.
- He only added healthy ingredients. - My gosh. Nice.
It's tasty too.
(He washes the cup immediately on the spot.)
(Jumping down)
(Stretching)
Gureum.
(Feeling heavy)
All right. Gureum.
- He looks heavy. - How cute.
- How cute. - Cats usually try to escape.
- What a friendly cat. - Gureum weighs 7kg.
(He goes to the bathroom without taking a break.)
He's holding the 7kg cat with 1 arm.
(He finishes shaving without any break.)
Let's go.
My gosh.
(He puts on a cute hair sticker.)
(Then he opens up the fridge again.)
(He takes out the toner pads from the fridge.)
(Rubbing it on his face while walking)
He's good at multitasking.
(Thorough)
Gosh, he's really good at that.
- That's like washing the face. - That's impressive.
It's impressive.
You do it before washing your face?
I do it instead of washing my face.
(The shelf next to the mirror is filled with cosmetic products.)
- He has a lot of cosmetic products. - I think...
he has more than me.
(Sputtering)
(I should cut it with the scissors.)
He's frugal.
(He uses up everything in the tube after cutting it with the scissors.)
What's that? What are you applying on your face?
- What's that? - It must be face mask.
That's the collagen face mask.
- Yes. - You have a long self-care routine.
(He steps out after applying the face mask generously.)
(He grabs a chicken breast sausage from the freezer.)
Chicken breast.
But chicken breast sausages are tasty.
They just taste like sausages.
(Grabbing)
(He takes out a container from the fridge next.)
(Pickled celtuce)
Oh, celtuce.
(He plates a small amount, just enough for one meal.)
Pickled celtuce.
People usually have that at barbecue restaurants.
Right.
(He neatly places it on the tray.)
He's so meticulous.
I can see how meticulous he is.
(Cracking)
(He cracks open the eggs he boiled earlier.)
(They almost look like poached eggs.)
They're half-boiled eggs.
When I went to Malaysia,
a close friend of mine taught me this recipe.
You need 3 cups of boiling water to cook 2 eggs.
You must put on a lid and then wait.
How many minutes? Eight.
- He looks so proud. - I am proud.
Not a lot of people in Korea boil eggs this way.
Wait. Are you a foreigner?
It's not that. I went to Malaysia on a trip.
- A Korean resident in Malaysia... - Yes.
taught me this recipe.
It's different from soft-boiled eggs.
- I guess they're different. - They're like water.
- At bean sprout restaurants... - Right!
- Yes. - That's right.
they give you something similar with dried lavers on top.
(Reaching in)
(Sprinkling garlic sesame seeds on top of the eggs)
(Microwaved chicken breast sausages)
He prepared his meal so fast.
- Natto. - Natto.
You must care a lot about your health.
- And he plates them nicely too. - Yes.
(His meal is healthy and looks beautiful as well.)
(Wrapping)
(He cleans up right away too.)
(His protein-packed breakfast is ready.)
(Neat)
That looks great.
(Enjoy your food!)
(Enjoy your food too, Gureum.)
You're going to eat with the face mask on?
(He starts his meal with the face mask on.)
- I must eat it before it gets hard. - Gosh, that's tasty.
(Stirring)
I initially came up with this meal to lose weight.
(He's been having this meal to watch his figure.)
- It's great for losing weight. - Right.
Now, I eat this meal for my workout.
In a way, I stepped up.
I eat this meal almost every day.
When I used to exercise and perform on stage,
I could feel that my stamina wasn't stable.
- Your balance was disrupted. - I wanted to maintain the balance.
So I ended up with this routine.
You kept experimenting on yourself.
- You're correct. - That's how you did it.
"You're correct."
- Correct. - Correct.
(The meal he settled on after many experiments)
He has the perfect tray for it.
That looks good.
(He has a bite of the rice too.)
(Slurping)
(He slurps the natto as if he was eating noodles.)
(Pouring out all the natto on top of his rice)
That looks good.
- It is. - With the rice.
It tastes good with the eggs too.
(Sighing)
I should have done that.
(Munching)
(I'm done eating.)
(Give me a treat.)
Gureum isn't pestering him for it.
- Right. - I'm sorry.
(Gureum waits for the treat.)
(Spotting Gureum)
(Yes, I'm right here.)
How cute.
Eat.
(Eating it right away)
(Look at you, enjoying it.)
(He grabs his plate again.)
The eggs.
(Slurping the eggs too)
(He finishes everything.)
- He finished everything. - Everything.
(I had a good meal too.)
(He grabs the empty plates...)
(and washes them without any delay.)
(Thorough)
Gosh, really?
I've never seen anyone use that for their kitchen sink.
(Sliding)
When I was young, my father taught me...
those cleaning tricks.
And they stuck with me.
That's a good tip.
I want to buy that too.
- I'm sure you have it at home. - Probably.
I can't find it. So I'll buy it.
So we can hold another bazaar.
(A big picture for the bazaar)
(Perfectly cleaning the area around the sink too)
It feels great when you remove all the moisture.
Right.
(Clean)
(He's done eating breakfast and cleaning up by 10:15am.)
What?
Earrings?
(What are these stickers for?)
(Pressing hard)
It's called auricular acupuncture.
It reduces facial swelling.
These are ear seeds.
- I see. I know what they are. - So...
you can put the ear seeds...
on the parts of your choice for some time.
Then your facial swelling would go away.
Facial swelling isn't the only benefit, though.
It improves your blood circulation.
And it also...
alleviates stiffness in your shoulders.
I came across this routine for the sake of my health.
It's a valuable item.
Having them on your ears gives you many benefits.
It's good for your eyes and improves your kidney function.
It's acupressure therapy.
Why are you so interested in health?
- It improves kidney function too? - Seriously.
You'll live a long healthy life.
- I do it for my health. - Yes. That's great.
That's fascinating.
(He's a planner who's used to following routines.)
You put them in a lot of places.
(Ear seeds cover up his ear in no time.)
(Go away, morning puffiness.)
That's fascinating.
Do you put them where you need help or just everywhere?
I just put them wherever I want.
People want them to look cute,
so some of them come in star shapes.
Okay. Good.
He's so diligent.
(The creature of habit finishes a self-care routine after his meal.)
(Then he naturally goes somewhere.)
(Opening up the closet)
(Rummaging through)
(He takes something out...)
(from between his clothes.)
A ukulele?
(A mysterious bag and a ukulele?)
(Humming)
(An electric keyboard is in the bag.)
(Getting up again)
(He grabs the Bluetooth microphone and comes back.)
I live in a small studio,
so I need to stack them up neatly in the closet.
I take them out whenever I need them.
(Turning on the Bluetooth microphone)
- One, two, three. - What?
(A song plays.)
(A sleepless place)
(Where neon signs glow)
(He suddenly starts singing.)
(Raising his hand)
He's a great singer.
(Showing off an extraordinary singing skill)
I majored in Vocal Performance for Musical Theater.
I joined an ensemble at the start of my career.
(He gained experience in various musicals.)
- "Rebecca." - Over there.
(Na Ra in "Rebecca")
(He perfectly played one of the Angels in "Kinky Boots.")
(He has become a musical actor everyone can count on.)
His vocalization is amazing.
He does have a different vibe when he's performing.
I'm performing and filming dramas at the same time.
I practice and read scripts whenever I have time.
- I'm trying to stay sharp. - To stay sharp.
(Turning sharply)
(Singing passionately)
That's the vocalization of musical singers.
(Putting on a musical show at home)
(Finishing up)
Do you live on the rooftop?
- Can you sing like that at home? - Right.
The walls are pretty thick.
- It's well soundproofed? - It's well soundproofed.
(He keeps practicing, forgetting about time.)
He's so good.
But you're not going to remove the face mask?
I forgot.
(As he's completely absorbed...)
I forgot to take it off.
(the face pack dries up.)
The face mask practically became another layer of your skin.
It's all dry now.
(Darn)
It's time to remove it.
(He puts the instruments back in their places.)
- Putting them back is hard. - Right.
- Right? - His studio would feel smaller...
- Right. - if he puts them in random places.
Right.
(Rolling)
- It dried up nicely. - Yes.
(It rolls off nicely thanks to his long practice session.)
(Careful)
- Gosh, your skin is glowing... - That looks good.
- Yes. It's glowing. - right now.
(Smiling)
I should stretch now.
(I should warm up my body after a vocal warm-up.)
(Clicking)
(Looking for a companion video for his workout routine)
(He picks "Extreme 84.")
- My gosh. - He's watching a fun show.
Actually, I watched almost 90 percent...
of all your variety shows.
Really?
I'm a huge fan.
(A truly devoted fan)
- Really? - Yes.
(Lips twitching)
- Why? - I've been a fan for a long time.
- Really? - I mean it.
- Thank you. - My gosh.
- Your face is getting red. - I wanted to shake your hand.
(Honored)
A lot of cool guys are my fans.
Thank you.
(You've got good taste.)
(With his eyes fixed on his favorite entertainer,)
(he begins to stretch.)
(Cracking)
- Won't his toes break? - Seriously.
Are you breaking them?
(By any chance, are you breaking them?)
It's like knuckle cracking.
- Totally. - I'm stretching the joints.
- You know what it is. - Yes. You totally have to do it.
(Rubbing)
(Stretching)
- He's flexible. - He's very flexible.
He has the body of someone who has exercised for many years.
- That's right. - Yes.
Okay.
(After a quick stretch,)
(Na Ra changes to new clothes.)
- He must be going out. - I know.
- It looks like he'll exercise. - It looks like he'll run.
(Will he run?)
(He brings shoes inside.)
Those are running shoes.
(He ties the shoelaces tightly.)
- Will he exercise inside the house? - Will he run in there?
(Will he run inside the house?)
What?
(He takes something out of the closet again.)
- What? - What's that?
Things keep coming out of a place.
Seriously.
- Every time... - If you open the closet,
- there'll be more space. - Yes.
It'll connect to a neighboring apartment.
His neighbors will throw in the items.
"Here you go."
(The mysterious and magical closet brings many guesses.)
(He takes a black object out of the magical closet.)
- What's that? - What's that?
It looks like dried laver for rolling gimbap.
(It's hard to guess the purpose of this object.)
(He even wears plastic bags over the shoes.)
What's that?
(Getting up)
Oh, my.
- It's what speed skaters use. - Okay.
- It's slippery. - That's right.
He's so eccentric.
(It's an unusual sight.)
There are only a few ways...
I can do aerobic exercise in this small apartment.
I've tried many different things.
I don't think there's another exercise...
that makes me sweat faster.
In this limited space, it's the one and only exercise.
I don't buy useless items.
It's really tough.
- I saw it on social media. - Really?
- Me too. - I wondered if anyone used it.
- I guess people actually use it. - I've used it for three years.
- You've used it for a long time. - Yes.
It's my first time seeing someone who uses everything he buys.
- Seriously. - I buy many items too.
(I buy many items too, but...)
(He's covered in sweat.)
(He takes off the long-sleeved top.)
Oh, my. He has no excess body fat.
That's...
(Shall I exercise in earnest?)
(Breathing out)
(The high-intensity aerobic exercise...)
(continues endlessly.)
It must be very tough on the legs.
(Laughing)
Why would you do the exercise not even Kwak Yoon Gy does?
Kwak Yoon Gy.
(His passion matches that of a national athlete.)
Stop.
I can tell that it's intense.
- He's drenched in sweat. - Look at that sweat.
(He's sweating buckets.)
(He feels refreshed.)
It's nice.
(At 12:08pm, the exercise ends.)
It's still noon.
(That's incredible.)
(He stores the mat inside the magical closet again.)
(After the busy morning routine,)
I wonder what he'll do.
(the routine man carefully puts on one layer at a time.)
- He'll run. - He'll go out.
He'll run. I'm 100 percent sure.
Will he run after that exercise?
(Impressive)
(Shall I get going?)
The corridor tells me that the building is old.
- That's right. - That's right.
Seriously.
(Warming up)
What's that in his hand?
- I know. When you run, - Right?
you can't have anything in your hands.
- You can't run with that. - Seriously.
(Heave-ho)
He's running with that?
He's extraordinary.
(With the shopping bag in his arms,)
(he arrives at a place.)
It's Seoul Children's Grand Park.
(It's Seoul Children's Grand Park!)
- That place has improved a lot. - It's a nice place.
It's a great spot for running.
That's right.
(Runner Na Ra enters in a natural way.)
(Running over)
(Looking around)
What?
(He hides the shopping bag inside the bush.)
Oh, my.
You can hide your belongings before running.
- That's right. - You can do it like a raccoon.
(Like a raccoon)
Let's go.
(Okay. Good.)
(He stores his bag in the eco-friendly locker.)
(Why did Na Ra stop after a short while?)
(Staring)
Na Ra.
Hey!
(Someone walks over to Na Ra.)
- Who is that? - Who is that?
It's Ryeo Un.
(Jang Woo's eating mate who's 12 years younger than him)
He's Jang Woo's junior.
(He has a huge appetite...)
(which matches Jang Woo's.)
(Actor Ryeo Un)
(He played a just character...)
(in the drama, "Weak Hero Class 2.")
(He played Bae Na Ra's biggest rival.)
He's one of the few friends...
with whom I can share my inner thoughts.
Are you guys that close?
When I was at the height of enjoying running last year,
I was supposed to meet up with Ryeo Un.
I ran all the way to the place we were supposed to meet.
I didn't want to enjoy it alone,
so I suggested that we run together.
But he kept running away.
That was why I called him over today.
I began running...
- after watching I Live Alone. - Really?
- Yes. For real. - Kian84 was a big influence on you.
That was why I said earlier that I loved you.
Really?
- Didn't you run before? - No, I didn't.
- Why is it always like that? - Me or Kian84.
Many people began running because of me.
But I haven't seen anyone who began running because of you.
Many people stopped running because of me.
He ended the trend.
(The entrance and exit of the running scene)
I told you to dress warmly.
I'm dressed warmly.
I bet you wore this outfit because you didn't want to run.
It isn't like that.
- That isn't an outfit for running. - That isn't an outfit for running.
I've never seen a runner in a long padded jacket.
I wore an appropriate outfit for running.
- Aren't you cold? - What?
- Aren't you cold? - Hey!
I told you put on a mask!
- I don't have a mask at home. - Really?
- He has no intention to run. - No.
I think he came out to eat.
They can go to a cafe together.
(It looks like he came out to eat.)
Let's warm up lightly and start running.
Three, four, five,
six, seven, eight.
To the back. One, two, three, four, five,
- He's wearing regular sneakers. - You're right.
While Ryeo Un likes to exercise,
he prefers tough sports.
I should buy you running shoes so that you can exercise.
(I should buy you running shoes.)
We won't run fast. We'll run slowly.
- Shall we run lightly? - Okay.
(They set out together.)
I can't run outside these days because it's so cold.
(That's impressive.)
- This place is great for running. - I see.
- There are a zoo... - I see.
and an amusement park.
I want to go to the zoo.
- The zoo? - Yes.
We'll reach the zoo if we go that way.
Okay.
His body is light.
Let's unleash this energy.
Hold on. It's an uphill road.
Yes.
It's an uphill road.
That's right. There's an uphill road.
Is it an uphill road?
It isn't hard.
That's why I'm not trying to run fast.
Just don't stop in the middle.
That's right.
- I want to stop. - No, just don't stop.
- If you're exhausted, - Okay.
you can walk fast.
His running speed is similar to mine.
No, he's much faster.
- Really? - Don't be ridiculous.
Your running pace is 12 minutes per kilometer.
- I stopped in the middle. - It isn't much of a running pace.
Since it was Ryeo Un's first time running,
- I had to adjust to his pace. - Okay.
- Did you adjust to Ryeo Un's pace? - Yes.
Don't take long strides when you go uphill.
Keep them small so that your feet move fast.
- Go up like this. - Na Ra, we're going too fast.
Let's go slowly.
- He's walking. - He's walking.
I can relate to him.
(I can relate to Ryeo Un.)
I just want to enjoy this fun activity with you.
Fun?
- When does it become fun? - If you become ambitious,
- you can run fast. - When does it become fun?
All right.
- It'll be fun when we go there. - Why aren't you listening to me?
- It'll be fun when we go there. - Really?
It'll be fun.
(Trust me.)
(Glancing over)
- Is there an amusement park? - It's an amusement park.
- What? - It feels great to come here.
- Na Ra, I've been here. - It has been a while.
(It's the amusement park from the childhood memories.)
(It's full of fun rides.)
Let's ride the carousel.
What? What did you say?
Two adults for the carousel.
It has been a while since I rode the carousel.
What? That's so sudden.
This is more of a fun run.
(Happy to see an ally)
- I bet you were exhausted too. - Why are you riding the carousel?
I thought they'd have an intense run.
I thought the running pace would be 4 minutes and 30 seconds.
It's nice.
(The comfortable course makes Ryeo Un happy.)
I wanted to finish the run...
even if it required a carousel ride. Yes.
Running fast wasn't important.
I put the focus on the enjoyment.
- I think it became a fun run. - A fun run. That's right.
(That's exactly what Moorathoner has said!)
Do you want to join?
(The fun run crew)
I've heard that somewhere.
Kian84 is disappointed.
I'm sad that he has a connection with you.
- He shouldn't be like that. - He's more of a fun run.
Hello.
(He says hello to children in a fun way.)
That's how it should be. It shouldn't be stressful.
- This is fun. - I know.
- It's comfortable and nice. - I'm sleepy. I'm about to sleep.
- Hey. - Oh, no.
Oh, no.
- Calm down, Na Ra. - I am calm.
Your stamina is no joke.
- You keep... - Of course!
(He runs uphill.)
You shouldn't overdo it when you have a fun run.
You shouldn't go uphill when you have a fun run.
- You would've eaten something. - I would've eaten something.
I would've had takoyaki.
(Eating)
While I support the fun run,
I think the records are important.
(He doesn't disappoint.)
It won't take much longer. We're nearly done.
We're almost there.
Run with your knees only.
That's it. Run with that mindset.
- Run with that mindset. - That's right.
We ran 2km.
- Did you say 2km? - Yes, we ran 2km.
That means we're done.
I thought that you'd get exhausted sooner.
- I'm exhausted, Na Ra. - No.
- I've been exhausted for a while. - No.
What do you mean, "No?" I'm telling you it's true.
You should run at least 3km.
I was going to run 5km with you.
You don't stop talking.
Do you usually talk a lot?
When I go outside...
- You talk to other people. - Yes, I talk to other people a lot.
I chat.
We're nearly done. I'm serious.
You just need to run a bit more. I'm serious.
You're exhausted now, right?
If you think of it in a broad sense, this is nothing compared to...
the many things that are happening in the world.
That kind of talk will make him lose energy.
Enjoy it.
- Why is there another uphill road? - It's okay.
If I push you from the back, it'll be easy to go uphill.
Really?
(He runs with the exhausted Ryeo Un until the end.)
Let's make a big circle.
The number isn't clean.
- You should run 4km. - We should run 4km.
All right. We're nearly done. We just need 80m.
We just need 30m.
(Hands-on coaching to complete the race)
We just need 20m.
Cheer up!
Okay. We're done.
Well done. All right.
Well done.
(They ran 4km at a running pace of 10 minutes per kilometer.)
Ten minutes per kilometer.
Ryeo Un ran with me.
I'm thankful for his consideration.
- You said you were thirsty. - Yes.
- Is that what he brought? - Yes.
So that you wouldn't be thirsty,
(He retrieves his shopping bag from the bush.)
I brought a healthy drink.
(What is it?)
- Here. - Is it what he drank earlier?
- It's what he drank earlier. - What's this?
It's tomato juice.
- How... - Just drink it from the bottle.
(He drinks it from the bottle.)
I packed one more, so drink it at home.
- Thank you. - Okay?
And open this.
What is it?
- What's this? - What's that?
- The stickers from earlier. - These are ear seeds.
They're amazing for removing puffiness.
- Really? - Yes.
Put them on before you get your makeup done,
and take them off right before the shoot.
Your puffiness will be gone.
- I'll use them well. - Don't mention it.
Doesn't it seem like a pyramid scheme?
Your puffiness will be gone.
I share things...
with people I love.
- You share things. - Yes.
- Well done. - Okay.
So, shall we run together next time as well?
Let's run in spring.
If you decide to run for real, I'll buy you running shoes.
- He promotes running. - I know.
I won't be able to accept those shoes.
- All right. You did well. - All right.
- Go. - I'll get going.
(After sending Ryeo Un off, Na Ra runs by himself.)
- It wasn't enough for him. - He takes long strides...
- because he has long legs. - He's fast.
(He runs fast.)
The wind is blowing against me.
It's cold.
It suddenly turned cold.
(He enters a place as he braves the strong wind.)
- It's a gopchang place. - It sounds delicious.
(A gopchang restaurant)
Hello.
Hello. Have you been well?
Happy New Year.
- Did you run here? - Yes, I ran here.
- I was running. - Really?
Yes.
I came here because I wanted to eat tasty gopchang.
- How nice. - You were on a diet earlier.
Don't you do that for lunch?
I make sure to eat one healthy meal a day.
I also eat what I want.
But in order to avoid eating at late hours,
I move up my mealtimes.
One serving of vegetable gopchang and one serving of fresh gopchang.
One serving each.
- Your regular order. - My regular order.
Thank you.
My goodness.
(The regular customer orders quickly.)
When I was little,
I often went to the market with my mom...
and ate vegetable gopchang.
- Really? - Yes.
This place has the most similar taste.
(Chatty)
I thought about which dish I ate...
- the most often. - Yes.
- This place came to my mind first. - Really?
- Yes. - First?
You're a chatterbox.
I like to approach people first.
When I was young, people often asked me,
"Are you in a bad mood?"
- So I smile a lot. - You have that face.
When I smile a lot,
I gain many opportunities to put other people...
in a good mood.
I told my actor friend about this place,
and he said that he wanted to visit.
- Really? - We'll come together sometime.
- Gosh. - It looks delicious.
(The gopchang is ready in no time.)
- They're good. - It looks so tasty.
Have a nice day. Bye.
(He takes the food to go.)
It should be eaten right away.
I know.
(Running)
(He runs home before the food gets cold.)
(My goodness)
- What? - Packages.
It was my birthday recently.
- Presents. - So people sent me presents.
For now...
(He hurriedly takes his pajamas and walks over to the restroom.)
I'll take these.
When you wash up and eat after exercising, it's a paradise.
(Refreshed)
- I mean... - He keeps doing that.
His skin will erode from putting on so many products.
He puts a lot of effort into his skin,
- but his touches are rough. - Yes.
(After moisturizing his skin with rough touches)
It's time to eat.
It'll be so tasty.
(All right.)
My goodness.
(He plates his favorite gopchang dish.)
Now...
(Taking)
Okay.
- You use a pretty plate. - Okay.
I'll eat it with lettuce.
I read this somewhere.
"When you make a dish for yourself,"
"you can improve your sense of self-worth."
- That's right. - That message made me think,
"Those words are for me!"
I think that's my influence as well.
- You're right. - Really?
Yes.
(Cook84 cooks to improve his sense of self-worth.)
It fills my sense of self-worth.
When I eat in a pretty and cool way,
it doubles my sense of self-worth.
Okay.
(Rummaging)
(Pretty glasses for Na Ra)
What? There are two.
(Struggling)
(He fills the glasses with long ice cubes.)
(Opening)
Then...
(What should I drink today?)
I'll drink this since I opened it.
My older brother is a distiller.
So he sends me samples to try.
(He pours the traditional liquor from his older brother.)
Coca-Cola too.
(He pours cold Coca-Cola in the other glass.)
Okay.
- Gosh, that looks so good. - That looks good.
It looks better than being in plastic containers.
Right.
Thank you for the food.
(Gulping)
(Groaning)
He downs everything.
- The first glass is always downed. - I love downing my drink as well.
The first glass is always downed.
My gosh.
He's eating it really well.
(Satisfied)
(He scoops it up with his spoon...)
(and eats it in one bite.)
He's eating well.
Right.
(A bite of the rice ball first...)
(and bite of the gopchang next)
This is it.
(Is it good?)
(He puts the glass noodles...)
(and gopchang into the wrap.)
This is what we live for.
I work out...
- to enjoy that. - Right.
(Letting out a breath)
(His sweat glands open.)
(He drinks the precious Korean traditional liquor.)
(He worked hard today...)
(and this is the reward for himself.)
I'll stop here.
Self-control.
It was because I had to perform the next day.
That's amazing.
(He turns around and puts down the spoon and chopsticks.)
(He cleans up efficiently from where he's sitting.)
It's easy to move around in a studio apartment.
- Right. - It's easy to move around.
Right. It's comfortable to get around the house.
(He skillfully captures the leftover food.)
(He spins it around...)
(and keeps it in the fridge.)
(After cleaning things up,)
(he takes the final sip.)
You should've had another glass with the leftover ice.
- Self-control. - I really wanted more,
but I stopped myself.
- You should have drunk hard liquor. - Right?
(He controls himself and brushes his teeth.)
- He never lazes around. - Right.
- All of a sudden? - To get rid of the dust.
I thought it was a restaurant ending the day.
That's how restaurants end the day.
"We're closing up now."
It was a day of consistency.
I believe it's important...
to fill the day with consistency.
- Gosh. - Gosh.
All of those things happened in that same place.
Right.
Doing things consistently...
all pile up.
Those things built up who I am now.
(It's time to rest for tomorrow's me.)
(Tapping)
(Jumping)
(A Person Called Na Ra Built by Consistency)
Gosh, that was great!
Thank you!
I could really relate to what you just said.
Doing things consistently all pile up...
to build up who you are.
It really reminded me to put that into practice.
He will wait for your comment the most.
- Bae Na Ra's role model. - Right.
Kian84.
Before a frog...
prepares for a leap,
there's a certain form it makes.
I think I've seen you say that on YouTube.
He's saying something he said elsewhere?
- He's using the same line. - Really?
He's using the same line he used elsewhere.
It wasn't even a great line,
- but he used it again. - We all prepare to leap.
- Leap? - Let's change it to "soar."
He was like a bird...
preparing to soar.
- Okay. - Right.
- A bird instead of a frog. - Right.
(I Live Alone)
(Cheer Up, Mr. Kim.)
"Cheer Up, Mr. Kim."
This place has changed so much.
(Dae Ho is standing in front of Cheongnyangni Station...)
(early in the morning.)
You're not going to meet your teacher, are you?
What time is it?
(Let's see.)
It's 9am. It's a tight schedule today.
It changed a lot.
- It changed so much. - Originally,
- there was something over here. - Isn't that Dae Ho?
Hey, Dae Ho!
- Who are they? - Who are they?
There are up to five men!
It's Jung Ho.
They traveled to Seoul.
It's his relatives.
(Dae Ho meets up with his relatives.)
- You're here. - It's great to see you.
Today, I invited my precious family members...
and cousins to Seoul.
(Dae Ho's family is famous for being a big family.)
- Right. - They are the cousins...
from back then.
(Has everyone come?)
(Look for those who are missing from your family.)
(A total of 10 siblings)
I asked each member,
and only these members could make it.
These many will gather...
for a great time.
- Many of them have come. - There are so many of them.
(They are planning to have a great time together.)
My eldest cousin, Kim Jung Ho.
Here you are.
(The icebreaker in the family)
He was the MC.
(MC Jung Ho)
My second eldest cousin, Kim Gun Ho.
Next is my younger brother, Sung Ho.
(Dae Ho's younger brother, Kim Sung Ho, 41)
- You just need to live there. - They look like each other.
(His younger brother with the exact same smile)
Kim Shin Ho.
My uncle's son. And Kim Sang Ho.
- All names end with "Ho." - He's the son of my youngest uncle.
(Sang Ho showed his dance moves for "24 Hours.")
That was when he just got out of the army.
Look at those moves.
As for Jung Ho,
he was handed over the family business in Yangpyeong.
He wasn't able to come to Seoul for around 20 years.
Even when he was busy with the restaurant,
he let us use part of his restaurant...
to have a cake ready...
along with different kinds of fruit.
He prepared the banner and birthday table for my father.
He prepared everything himself.
That banner is really touching.
He even prepared a banner.
He found a picture of my father when he was young.
(Thanks to Jung Ho who helped with the 70th birthday party,)
I will make sure to repay this moment.
(Dae Ho expressed his gratitude and promised to repay him.)
That was when I got that heart.
I wanted to thank my cousins separately.
That was how this occasion came to be.
Since my cousins all lived in Yangpyeong,
I wanted them to be away from that area...
and gift them a special day.
That was why I told them to come to Seoul.
To repay for their kindness,
- you prepared the Dae Ho Tour. - Right.
They feel like brothers.
- They look really tight. - Right.
Gosh.
Since Jung Ho helped out with my father's 70th birthday,
I thought it would be a good idea...
to spend a good time with the cousins.
- What will we be doing? - What?
Just follow me for now. That's all you need to do.
- What is all this? - Gosh.
How long did it take on the KTX from Yangpyeong?
Around 30 minutes?
Somewhere around 30 minutes.
- It's a quick ride, isn't it? - Yes.
- It's my first time here. - What?
- It's your first time here? - Is it your first time, Gun Ho?
It's my first time here in around 20 years.
It was his first time on the KTX.
- It was my first time on the KTX. - Really?
I'm serious.
It has been so long since the KTX has been around.
I didn't have the chance.
Dae Ho upgraded our seats...
to the business class.
Business class?
They're not called business class seats these days.
- Then what are they called? - Executive seats.
- Executive seats. - Executive seats?
- Executive seats? - Right.
I tried to sound better from the premium seats.
Hey, Sang Ho. Why didn't Seon Ho come?
He's taking a winter session.
Are you serious?
I've never missed out on any session...
after getting discharged from the army.
Same here.
You've taken all sessions?
I think it's colder here than in Yangpyeong.
It's colder in Seoul.
It feels colder.
- We met before. - We're here.
(They arrive somewhere through the chilly wind.)
All right, everyone. For today,
this will be our feet.
- What is that? - I rented a car.
(I rented a car.)
- Let's clap. - Gosh.
- Really? - Yes.
(Stay away, cold winter breeze.)
The Damarghini won't be able to move with all of those people.
Of course not.
I needed a mini-bus to drive a lot of people.
As it was a special day,
I wanted to make them...
experience something they have never experienced.
That was how I made my decision.
- Were you the driver? - I did the driving.
Jung Ho always drove around the cousins.
I wanted Jung Ho to feel comfortable today.
(Leave everything to Dae Ho Tour today!)
- Really? - We'll move around with this.
- You got us a bus. - I'll be the one to drive.
- Can you drive this? - I can.
- I didn't know. - I can drive this size...
with the Class One license.
It's around four times bigger than the Damarghini.
(Excited)
Let's hurry up and get on since it's cold.
- He went this far for this? - It's my first time riding this.
- I didn't expect this. - Gosh.
I'm riding a lot of new things.
It's my first time riding this as well.
- What? - What?
Did we get too surprised?
Inside, there will be water and snacks for you.
Make yourself comfortable and I will drive you all...
to the next destination.
- All right. - I see.
Gosh.
Gosh, it feels so dull.
With this sight, it looks like they will go to an Internet cafe...
and play a game of billiards.
They will then head home after a bowl of gukbap.
You're right.
How does a picture sound before we depart?
A picture? Okay!
(A picture sounds good.)
One, two, three.
We never had the chance to meet like that in Seoul.
- Right. - Everyone must feel excited.
- Great. - Aren't you the only one...
who is going to look good in the picture?
- Are you sure about this? - It is a bit hard to get everyone.
- Our faces will be in it, right? - I do see everyone.
- Let's go! - Here we go!
- Let's go! - Go!
How long does it take to get there?
I can't tell you that.
We can't even know where we're going?
Shouldn't we get at least a brief explanation?
Shouldn't we be told where we're going?
We don't even know where we're headed to.
Any tour would announce where we're headed to.
It's more fun to go somewhere without knowing about it.
We might not be told what we're doing there,
but we could be told where we're headed to.
That's the most exciting moment.
We're able to be in a car like this and travel around Seoul...
thanks to Dae Ho.
It was my first time riding the KTX...
and it's my first time riding a car like this.
Gosh.
All I have left now is getting on a plane.
Take your time to look around.
- The river looks great. - It's nice.
The river in Seoul feels quite different.
- Gosh. - The river in Seoul?
There are hand warmers, Sung Ho. There's gimbap as well.
There were things prepared for us.
- Gosh! - There's gimbap as well?
- Here's some gimbap. - Gosh, thank you.
- Dae Ho prepared a lot. - Thank you.
You prepared food for them to have in the car as well?
They had to come early in the morning.
I thought they would feel hungry.
The service is excellent.
It was still a tour I planned for them.
Great.
As I'm taking a bite, it happens to be beef gimbap.
- Right. - Right. It's expensive gimbap.
It's not regular gimbap. It's beef gimbap.
Gosh, it's good.
It feels like a real trip when having gimbap in the car.
Right.
It's starting to feel like a trip with the gimbap.
- Right. - Right.
Dae Ho.
Gun Ho has some great news.
What is it?
Could it be...
(Chuckling)
I got a girlfriend.
(I got a girlfriend.)
Really?
You have a girlfriend?
Yes.
Gun Ho seems to be really into her.
- He's into her? - Gosh.
I've never seen him like that. He can't take his eyes off of her.
How long were you two together?
It just has been two weeks.
It has been two weeks?
It has been 13 days now.
We started seeing each other on Jan 1.
That's awesome.
It's their 22nd day soon.
(It's their 22nd day soon.)
Right.
We have to give them 20 cents.
- Right. - Their 22nd day.
Tell us more about your girlfriend.
(Gun Ho's exciting love story before his 22nd day)
What's the age difference between the two of you?
It's the ideal four-year age difference.
How did you meet her?
I was introduced to her by the father of a close friend.
That was how we met.
- She has a great personality. - What does she do?
She's an elementary school teacher.
A teacher?
(Impressed)
(They give out the best reaction.)
Why would a person like her...
(Joking)
It's a mystery to me as well.
Why would a person like her be with me?
But we really get along with each other.
Check out his confidence.
Did she watch the episode with all of us?
We watched it together.
- Really? - We watched it together...
and I explained things to her.
- Well, - And...
we don't have our ancestral rites anymore.
- Relieve her misunderstanding. - Right.
Tell her that we have dishwashers for business use.
Tell her to don't worry about anything.
Do you not have ancestral rites anymore?
We decided to cut down on our ancestral rites.
We just decided to simplify it...
and prepare just a small table with their pictures.
(Whenever Dae Ho's big family gathered,)
(the amount of food was on another level.)
- That's important news. - Right.
So for ancestral rites...
It feels like he wants people to be aware of this.
We just decided to have a meal together.
What about making thousands of kimchi?
We decided to buy our kimchi.
That's the best!
We'll use frozen dumplings.
- Frozen dumplings. - They're good.
- What about the braised ribs? - What?
The braised ribs.
We'll just go vegetarian.
- Right. - It's fine to buy food.
It's a Seoul tour, but it seems like we're getting away from Seoul.
That's not true.
What's certain is that this one is for Gun Ho.
- Really? - Yes.
There must be different themes for each course.
- Right. - I see.
- So the first course is for Gun Ho? - Yes.
Really?
This is Gyeonggi Province.
They must be moving quite a lot.
Hold on.
We're going to the airport.
- The airport? - Right.
- Are you going abroad? - This is the way...
to Incheon Airport.
Will Gun Ho be able to get on a plane today?
- I don't have a passport. - You don't?
(Wiping his nose)
I don't have a passport.
Just follow me.
(Just trust and follow me.)
That's all you need to do.
We're here.
(They arrive at the parking lot of Incheon Airport.)
- Thank you. - Gosh.
This is a historical day. It's Gun Ho's first time...
- at the airport. - Right.
(It's Gun Ho's first time at the airport.)
(Six grown men all walking over together)
What's going on?
- What is this? - It feels like "Nameless Gangster."
- What is this? - Follow me.
Aren't they going to eat at the airport?
It's a restaurant tour at the airport.
(We have come to take over a good airport restaurant.)
Every scene is hilarious.
- It's an exciting place to visit. - Right. With your suitcase.
- That's the best moment. - Right.
Getting ready and going to the airport feels exciting.
- Right. - Right.
- It's my first time here. - It's so clean.
Right.
- Gosh! - It's been a while.
- It's amazing. - It's great.
Shouldn't we take a picture to celebrate?
Do you know this, Gun Ho?
This is where you go after showing your plane ticket.
- Right. - These are the duty-free stores.
You can't go in this area freely.
- It's for travelers. - A ticket.
- You need a plane ticket. - Right.
That's where you go when you get on a plane.
What are they doing there?
It was a place Gun Ho has never been to before.
Why are you showing him that?
This feels a bit like a scam.
After asking for a lot of money.
That's where you go when you get on a plane.
Got it.
- I prepared this for Gun Ho. - Me?
(Keep following me.)
(They get seated somewhere after a small session.)
This is a cafe with a view of airplanes.
- I see. - A place where you can see them.
- Inside the airport? - Right.
(He wanted to show the planes to Gun Ho.)
It's a place you can enter without a passport.
So there's a place like that.
- You wanted to show him planes? - To see them up close.
So it's like a field trip.
It was meant to be a trip more than a field trip.
They came all the way from Cheongnyangni to see this?
- A lot of people visit the airport. - Right.
I also went to the airport when I was 25.
- Right. - Just to look around.
- It did make me feel excited. - Right.
So other than this lounge,
- there's nothing else to see. - I'm dumbfounded.
That's incredibly unique.
It's because...
It's because you can see the planes up close here.
Really?
Dae Ho prepared a lot for us.
Thank you. Gosh, thank you so much.
"Thank you."
"Thank you so much."
The youngest looks very upset.
But all of this...
feels like a sitcom, and I love it.
Actually...
It feels like "Honest Living."
- You don't need a passport here. - Right.
- You don't need it here. - Yes.
- It's my first time here. - You can drink tea as well.
Right.
I'm able to experience this place in advance.
- Right. - We'll be traveling in July.
- It's a rehearsal. - Right.
Gun Ho was able to come...
and find out where things are located.
(He's incredibly touched.)
It was Gun Ho's first time at the airport.
It would definitely look amazing.
He gets to see the big airplanes.
He doesn't have a passport as well.
I thought he would be amazed.
That was how I felt when I first went to the airport.
- Is that really all you went for? - Right.
- My gosh. - But...
when you first saw a plane,
wasn't it because you were headed somewhere?
- Right. - That was why you were amazed!
He found it to be fascinating.
- Who is fascinated? - Right there.
- Let's clink our cups. - Right.
- Cheers! - Let's do this, at least.
(Walking on eggshells)
- Right. - You can come with your girlfriend.
No one would've imagined this.
No one would've imagined this?
Getting up at 6am.
- And taking a train. - Taking a shower.
Taking a train to Seoul at 7am.
They're drinking coffee at Incheon Airport.
And we're drinking coffee at the airport?
When you go back home at night...
- It would definitely pop up. - and lay in bed,
it will be a great memory.
Right. "What did I do today?"
It's just the start.
(I see.)
Right.
- Right. - Let's go.
- Right. - He prepared a lot for us.
This is just an appetizer.
Let's go after taking a group photo.
- Okay. - Okay.
- This is nice. - Right.
We had to take a picture together.
It's free.
(Impressed)
- It's a place for photos. - They have that there as well?
What is this? Oh, it's a plane in the background.
They're all so cute.
No one is complaining.
(The Ho Brothers look like they're enjoying themselves.)
(This is quite fun.)
Gosh.
They're all so nice.
That looks nice. Sang Ho did a good job.
When would we ever stand in the runway like that?
I'm sorry to say this, but I feel quite embarrassed.
Right.
- This is fun. - It turned out to be okay.
- They had this here. - It turned out to be fun.
- You're all satisfied, right? - Yes.
- It was great. - Right.
- Was that free? - It was free.
- Nice one! - Nice one!
The atmosphere lightened up after that session.
- Let's move to the next spot. - So far, it's been okay.
- Today's busy. - It's been okay.
Thank you.
- What's this? - Seriously.
The photo turned out okay.
This isn't half bad.
You can enjoy the airport without flying out.
- I didn't know that. - Without flying out.
It was fun watching the planes.
Are we going back to Seoul?
To Cheongnyangni.
This is just starting.
What should we do now?
How long will it take to travel?
(Laughing)
About an hour.
You must've prepared a lot.
It took us some time to come,
- Right. - so it'll take at least an hour.
A tour is supposed to be hard.
I mean, it's...
- Gun Ho, you're not sleeping. - Are you sleeping, Gun Ho?
You're not sleeping, are you?
I'm trying to fight off sleep by drinking water,
but I'm really sleepy.
Two and a half hours was indeed long.
Of course. They traveled from Cheongnyangni to Incheon.
(While Gun Ho is fighting off sleep...)
- Is it here? - Yes.
(They enter the highway.)
I wonder where they're going next.
Traffic is getting heavier.
Is the second destination a secret as well?
Yes, it is, but...
When people went to do manual labor in the past,
they just hopped in when the van arrived.
You don't know where you're going and doing what.
Right. I've heard about it.
That's how it feels right now.
It does feel like they're being sold off.
Despite that...
I can only do this because we're cousins.
(Before they knew it, they arrived in Seoul.)
- We're back in Seoul. - Oh, you went back to Seoul.
How inefficient is that?
I don't know where we are, driving around like this.
- You can't... - Yes.
You can't tell...
- because we're driving, right? - Right. I can't tell.
You can see National Agricultural Cooperative Federation...
on your left, right?
This is where you claim your money when you win...
first prize in the lottery.
(Staring)
I should come here.
There should be an occasion for me to come here.
I have a ticket I haven't checked for this week.
I should get it exchanged.
- He's funny. - I should come here one day.
(Touching)
(Amused)
Are you checking it now?
- I... Before we set off... - You'd cash it in...
since you're here?
Yes, since I'm here. When else would I come?
"Potential 1.8 million dollars."
I think the second-prize winners cash it in here too.
Third-prize winners get a few thousand dollars.
Around 1,500 or 1,600 dollars?
It's between 1,000 and 2,000.
Right. That's why the third-prize winners should come here too.
Look at his face. Is his expression changing?
(Heart pounding)
- Go straight. - What?
We don't need to drop by.
- Should we just go? - Yes.
- Okay. - It's hard to win...
even five dollars these days.
(Upset)
You can only win five dollars if you have a lucky dream these days.
(Luck suddenly feels harder to come by.)
- You can't with just any dreams. - Exactly.
I can see Seoul Station now.
This is where all of us can relate to.
Relate?
I'm sure they're excited on the inside.
It's only starting.
What could it be? It is intriguing.
A hand warmer...
- Take a hand warmer each. - A hand warmer?
Are they doing something outside, since they're taking a hand warmer?
Have you all taken hand warmers?
- Yes. - Yes, we took one each.
- I... - I have it.
You must take it.
- Is it outside? - It must be outside.
We're doing something outside?
Dae Ho, go step by step.
- Dae Ho. - You're sweating, right?
(Making a fuss together)
We got to the ice rink in front of the City Hall.
(Set up in the middle of Seoul)
- That's a really famous spot. - It's really popular.
- In front of the City Hall? - Yes.
There was a small reservoir in the town.
When it froze hard,
we enjoyed winter sports there.
We went sledding on it.
Jung Ho always pulled by sled.
And Gun Ho pushed it from behind.
I have a memory of playing with them on the ice.
- I went sledding a lot in Yeoju. - Right?
It's a sled made of wooden planks nailed together, right?
- I used to ride that a lot too. - That's right.
We used a kitchen knife to sled.
- That's right. - A kitchen knife.
- One with a broken blade. - Right, with a broken blade.
- No way. - One with a broken blade.
That's right.
How do I do this?
I don't remember us skating together.
They're so cute. They're all going in a line.
- You said it'd bring back memories. - I know.
You said it'd bring back memories.
- You said it'd bring back memories! - Darn. Old memories...
Old memories...
- It's on your clothes. - No one can skate well.
No one can skate.
Why did you go there?
- To make memories on the ice. - For memories.
(Even the guide is a beginner.)
I'd never skated too.
(The Ho brothers are struggling on the ice.)
(Shouting)
(Flailing about)
Oh, no.
It was so hard.
(Falling here and there)
(They all fall together.)
- Would you be okay tomorrow? - Shouldn't he feed us...
before making us skate?
- Right. You should eat. - They hadn't had any food...
since they had gimbap.
Let's rest now. My goodness.
I should've taken tomorrow off too.
I know. This is bad.
(Sighing)
(Panting)
(Everyone is moaning.)
They're all about to die.
Still, it was fun.
- It was fun, indeed. - It was fun.
- They're satisfied. - Yes, they're getting satisfied.
- They're getting satisfied. - It's been long since I skated.
- You don't get to skate like this. - I know.
Let's go and have some snacks.
Order whatever you want.
There's fishcake. Yes.
First of all... One, two, three, four, five...
(A snack bar where Dae Ho will treat everyone)
You need a hot soup when it's cold.
(Fishcake and udon that'll warm you up)
(And the nation's favorite snack, tteokbokki)
Was it a build-up to eat that?
Shall we order about four servings of tteokbokki?
- Shall we have a fishcake skewer? - We must have that.
Let's order just two drinks.
- Thank you for the food. - Goodness.
Let's go.
- Thank you for the food. - Thank you for the food.
Enjoy your food.
(The long-awaited first bite)
(Exclaiming)
(Taking a bite of the fishcake)
It tastes better after being out in the cold.
I know.
It's so good.
They're eating hurriedly.
(Eating hurriedly)
Put the noodles in here?
- Yes, in the soup. - This is good.
Everyone must've been hungry.
(Feeling bad)
Our memories...
Memories... I mean...
Is there another spot of our memories?
He's hoping there isn't.
What? There's one more?
You see?
He's checking, hoping there won't be.
- There are many spots left. - Oh, really?
Couldn't you share a little about our next destination?
The next spot we're going to...
(The next spot is...)
I bet you've never been there.
Can we not go?
(Joking)
The spot you've never been to.
(To the unexplored spot)
(Following without knowing anything)
What is it?
We're going uphill?
The climax was...
"How can I trigger their dopamine rush?"
I gave it a lot of thought.
"A place they can't even imagine. Where could it be?"
"What shall we do?"
(Where could that place be?)
My place.
Come in.
It's different from what I saw on TV.
(It's different from what I saw.)
- Let's go. Let's go in. - Welcome.
It's the beach!
(Daeundae unfolds when you open the gate.)
This is the beach.
(The ultimate dream, a home sauna)
I'm really envious of it.
(And a living mini-ecosystem, vivarium)
He really is an expert.
(The landmark of Mount Inwang)
It really is unusual.
He's a natural person.
I do want to visit it once.
- It's really interesting. - Right.
Oh, this is the beach you made.
It's a complete mess.
(The sand paradise is still there.)
Come in, everyone.
- Can I come in with my shoes on? - Yes, you can.
(Come in with your shoes on.)
When on earth are you going to get rid of the sand?
There's sand everywhere.
No idea.
This is the sauna and a bath.
It looks bigger in person.
I use the sauna really well.
I think the sauna is the best part of your house.
(Dae Ho shows the house around.)
This is like a greenhouse.
These are vivariums.
- I grow plants too. - Look at this.
It smells like mushroom.
Right. It's like a greenhouse.
Gosh, this...
- There's a lizard too. - There's a lizard.
Do you want to see the other house too?
- The other house? - Do we have to go out?
- No, we can go across from here. - Do we...
- What? - What?
We should check it out since we're here.
When else would we come back?
- Gosh, this is the roof. - That's right.
Be careful.
Earlier...
(Laughing)
Goodness.
It's a bit slippery as it's winter.
I get to see the view I only saw on TV.
- Be careful. - This is it, right, Dae Ho?
That's right.
- Here... - You should take a photo.
(Dae Ho's house doesn't feel unfamiliar.)
When else would we have a chance to take a photo together here?
Of course.
- Here. One... - It's cold.
One, two, three.
- Nice. - So they took a photo together.
We got it. Be careful going down.
(Sliding)
- Be careful. - Be careful.
You should watch out here.
(You must stay alert at all times here.)
- Be careful. - It's slippery.
Once you let your guard down here,
- you must call an ambulance. - Seriously.
Everywhere is life-threatening.
(Chuckling)
This is where I stay.
- Look at that. - It's...
- Oh, it's here? - Take a look around.
You live such a dynamic life.
Your mom must've been shocked.
I told you. Mom cried after seeing the place.
- For real? - It's quite clean...
compared to other days.
But it's quite clean.
- It's rather clean today. - Is that so?
Since my cousins were coming...
I cleaned it up.
Nana.
- Where is Nana? - There he is.
- It's my first time seeing him. - Nana.
Say hello. They're my cousins.
He must've eaten a lot.
- His belly is full. - Yes, it's full.
How cute.
All right. Now,
let's take some stuff from here and go back up.
For dinner,
I need to make something.
- I needed to serve them well. - Right.
- You don't do it half-heartedly. - Oh, you're making something?
Why on earth do you have this at home?
What is this?
Oh, my stuff...
- What? - Why do you have the delivery box?
Look at this.
- What is it? - I use it to move things at once.
It's difficult to go back and forth.
(An all-in-one delivery box to move stuff around)
Because I use both floors...
Because it's inconvenient to move things upstairs?
- Exactly. - I see.
- He's right. - Let's go.
Be careful.
(Careful)
Gosh.
(They're back at house number 2.)
Gosh, I'm so sick of this.
Seriously.
Yes, that. There's oyster in the fridge.
- There is oyster? - Yes.
Where?
Since it's the New Year,
I'm going to make oyster maesaengi rice cake soup with dumplings,
using the ingredients in season.
When I was in school,
I'd visit Yangpyeong on January 1.
There's a mountain there too,
so we'd go up and see the sunrise. When we came down,
the whole town made rice cake soup together...
to welcome the New Year.
We'd eat together at home.
I used to sit next to them...
and make it together.
I wanted to bring back that memory.
I decided to make rice cake soup with dumplings...
- to make it meaningful. - Rice cake soup with dumplings.
Since it's the New Year.
(Putting it in right away)
Shouldn't you separate the rice cakes before putting them in?
No, I can just...
stir it.
"Stir it?"
Hey, be glad he didn't add the whole rice cake stick.
(Let's trust Dae Ho and wait.)
Dae Ho, you know what we like.
- Yes, I do. - Put everything in at once...
and boil it.
- Right. - Not separately.
That's for sure.
That's it. I just need to boil it now.
I think it'll be delicious. It smells good.
Now, we have an important agenda.
We have an important agenda.
I should cut this and use it.
(Rummaging through)
- This... - What shall we do?
Cut it into pieces according to the number of people.
Cut it into five pieces.
That wasn't all.
You must be drawing lots.
Here... While that boils,
we'll draw lots.
(Interested)
He even prepared an event.
I prepared a tour meticulously.
I thought of many things,
but I decided to go with drawing lots for gifts.
I learned this from Jung Ho as well.
Just like how we give out New Year's cash gift,
I wanted it to be nerve-racking and thrilling.
So I prepared gifts with different values.
I didn't reveal what they were.
The higher the rank, the better, right?
- It should be. - The quality, that is.
We just need to write the middle characters of our names.
Is that so?
To make it as subtle as possible,
- I'll crumple them. - The odds of winning are high.
Of course. First...
The first gift.
What did you prepare?
- What's that? - First...
(He brought out a bag.)
It's the first gift.
- What could it be? - For fifth place.
I'll draw it from here.
(He draws lots inside the delivery box.)
- That's state-of-the-art. - The delivery box.
- I drew one. - Drum roll.
- You're drawing one by one? - Yes, I am.
Since there are 5 of you, I'll go for 5th place first.
A lucky draw is the most fun.
There's nothing else that lifts the mood like a lucky draw.
- Why is this making me nervous? - It's nerve-racking.
We're nervous because of this.
We're hoping not to get that.
I hope it's not my name.
- This is for 5th place? - Yes, it's for 5th place.
I have no idea what it is.
- If I can't beat the odds... - The gift for fifth place...
It goes to Kim Jung Ho!
- Goodness. - The eldest got it.
Nice!
- We'll present you with the gift. - Great.
He got that because of what he just said.
All right.
(Getting up reluctantly)
- Jung Ho. - I really hoped...
that I wouldn't win this.
I'm always grateful for you. Here you go.
I bought it from a department store.
(Is that so?)
Congratulations.
- It's beef jerky. - It's beef jerky.
- Oh, you got beef jerky? - Yes.
I'll reveal the next gift.
(Presenting the gift for 4th place next)
I don't get another chance if I win one?
- It's over once you're picked. - Of course.
But the gift for fifth place...
- isn't so bad. - It's not bad.
You're right.
- The next gift. - That's not true.
- The higher, the better. - I know. Gosh.
(He still can't let go.)
- It's a box. - The box is big.
All right.
(I'm drawing a name, excluding Jung Ho.)
I'm nervous because this year's fortune...
- Jung Ho... - This is...
(Anxious)
I drew one.
Gun Ho!
- They shouldn't say anything. - Yes! Nice!
(It's festive except for Gun Ho.)
Since Gun Ho gets cold easily, I give you hand warmers!
(The gift for 4th place, hand warmers)
- This is better. - He's really disappointed.
Yours is better.
Kim Sang Ho!
- Look at him. - Yes!
(Laughing)
Hey, that's natural sea salt.
- It's a condiment set. - Condiments?
(The gift for 3rd place, 5-condiment set)
(How jealous!)
I'll be a good son to my mom.
- It's the real deal from now. - The real deal?
It should be the real deal now.
They can't yield them.
Is the price a lot higher?
Is the price different big or small?
- It's a lot more expensive. - Is it?
(Heart pounding)
This is the real deal.
Just tell us that.
I'll reveal the gift for 2nd place 1st.
- Second place. - The gift for second place...
- It must be liquor. - What is it?
A Bluetooth speaker.
I have a Bluetooth speaker at home.
Then switch it with mine.
The gift for first place...
I splurged on it.
What is it?
Did he spend a lot?
He spends a lot on things like this.
When he gives out gifts.
Is it not inside?
What is it?
It looks like it's from a luxury brand.
It's from Bottega Veneta.
It really is a luxury brand.
I don't know about luxury brands.
- You guys have no idea, - It's somewhat...
so you're not happy with it.
- They're like, "Veneta what?" - My cousins...
don't really know about luxury brands.
For your information,
it's about 600 dollars.
(A gift that costs around 600 dollars)
(I don't know what that is, but I want it.)
- It's only for the two of us. - What a bummer.
(Upset)
- First place! - You're drawing first place, right?
(Who is the real lucky guy?)
I drew it!
I've never won in lucky draws.
Even I'm nervous.
(Kim Sung Ho versus Kim Shin Ho)
Would you read it for me?
Since you're the eldest?
I'll announce the winner in his place.
(MC Jung Ho, 5th place)
The biggest beneficiary of today's trip...
The first place winner is...
(Who is the biggest beneficiary of today's trip?)
Shin!
(Kim Shin Ho)
(Oh, my goodness!)
Shin!
(Grunting)
(My first luxury brand gift...)
It's the first luxury brand I bought.
(Lady Luck is on Shin Ho's side.)
We can't help but applaud.
- He's so excited. - He's exhilarated.
He's never bought a luxury brand either.
Right. It's expensive.
That's really disappointing.
(Can't help but disappointed)
The second prize gift, the Bluetooth speaker!
(2nd place winner Sung Ho gets the Bluetooth speaker.)
(I have it at home...)
Sir, I really need that.
Would you switch...
Thank you so much.
You can have them both.
I have a Bluetooth speaker at home.
Then I'll share the beef jerky as our drinking snack.
Thank you.
Gosh, this gives such a dopamine rush.
You're lucky from the beginning of the New Year.
I know.
This is 600 dollars?
(The gift for 1st place, a card wallet from a luxury brand)
- A card wallet. - A card wallet.
It's nice to get a gift like that.
- That's right. - It's too much to get it for me.
That's right.
(Jealous)
You're so lucky.
I should carry it around all the time.
- All right. - Thank you.
It's heartwarming.
Everyone.
Our dopamine rush isn't over yet.
- There's more? - Yes, there is.
- There's more? - Let's eat first to calm down.
Oh, right. They had to eat.
(Exclaiming)
The smell of green onions fills the room.
Dae Ho, you prepared a lot.
He became sweet...
- after winning the wallet. - Right?
(It was cooked thoroughly while they were playing.)
Maesaengi.
- It looks good. - It looks so good, though.
Dae Ho is a good cook.
- Thank you for the food. - Thank you for the food. Enjoy.
Gosh, I get to have rice cake soup only now.
(The eldest tries the soup first.)
(Grunting)
Maesaengi rice cake soup.
(The biggest beneficiary of the trip Shin Ho, warms up with soup too.)
Goodness.
- How does it taste so good? - It's good.
- It's really good. - It's good.
That's the most well-received.
Everyone's warmed up by it.
It's incredible as it has maesaengi.
It's so good. It's refreshing.
- It's good. - How does it taste so good?
It's good.
It's like having a meal during the holiday after ancestral rites.
We'd gather like this and eat.
- I know. - This sight is kind of cute.
I know, right? It's so...
(Inhaling without a break)
It's been a while since I enjoyed rice cake soup.
Fortunately, they emptied their bowls.
It must've been really good.
They must've been tired.
(Drinking up as they went through a lot)
Dae Ho prepared many things today.
It feels different to see you here instead of Yangpyeong.
When else will we get a chance to gather in Seoul...
and hang out like this?
Right. The gathering itself is nice.
Jung Ho prepared my father's 70th birthday party too.
- I see - Right.
When I went, my parents looked so happy.
My mom was really happy.
So I thought, "Did I think too complacently about it?"
I got such thoughts.
- It's because I have experience. - Exactly.
Our parents might say that they don't want it,
and they want it to be a simple family meal.
- But it's not what we should do. - Right.
We need to hold them a party,
- so it lasts in our memory. - That's right.
Actually, a lot more family members...
gathered for his 70th birthday party.
- My dad choked up too. - That's right.
When he talked...
My dad... He's not the type to cry. I've never seen him cry.
He's a Thinking type.
He barely managed to talk.
(Gosh, he barely managed to talk.)
If he went on a bit more, he'd have cried his eyes out.
I was really surprised.
I felt really grateful to Jung Ho.
He's been taking care of us both materially and emotionally.
Also, he always spared his time for us...
and led us.
I actually prepared this trip to thank Jung Ho.
Should I turn on some music for the background?
That's why we're gathered, actually.
- I wanted to express my gratitude. - That's right.
- So... - I agree.
Actually...
Earlier...
(Rummaging)
- What is it? - I thought of how to deliver it.
I wrote something for him, letter by letter.
- A letter? - Gosh, he prepared that too.
(Goodness, he's seriously...)
Shin Ho, turn on some music.
It's nothing much.
(Focused)
- Darn. I don't think I can read it. - Come on.
After he got over 40...
Why would you cry?
He became strange after he got over 40.
You really are sentimental.
I'm the Feeling type. Don't.
- First of all... - He's reading it.
"Dear my beloved cousins."
(Dear my beloved cousins.)
"Thank you for always keeping my side like actual brothers."
"Whenever I went to Yangpyeong during the holiday..."
"when I was young,"
"I didn't want to go back home,"
"so I remember how I always cried and threw a tantrum."
What's wrong with me?
"During summer, we'd cook by the stream,"
"have baeksuk, and swim together."
"During winter, we'd play soccer on the frozen Yonggol Stream."
"I miss the time when we hung out together,"
"going from this mountain to that."
(I miss that time.)
Darn, I wasn't going to cry.
(Even if he tries to fight it off, he can't help but get teary.)
- It's so sudden. - What do we do?
What? He's crying?
(Holding back their laugh)
(Hanging his head)
Why are you laughing, CODE KUNST?
It's a very touching moment.
The genre changes so fast.
- I mean... - The genre changed like this.
What are you doing all of a sudden while having rice cake soup?
It's because there was no build-up.
It switched all of a sudden. He did the same before.
- It's the same vibe from before. - I know.
Why does it make me laugh so much whenever Dae Ho cries?
Once I can't stop controlling my tears,
I become dramatically sentimental.
- Right. - You must get immersed really fast.
Well, this is...
His eyes are really red.
I think you're going through andropause.
Look at his eyes.
"And our captain, Jung Ho,"
"who took care of the younger ones."
- "Now..." - Stop it.
Gosh.
(The brothers are choked up as they're grateful toward the eldest.)
- They're all so warmhearted. - Goodness.
"Now that you're aged,"
"you pass out first when we drink during the holiday."
"We'll support you from now."
"You can pass out all you want."
(You can pass out all you want.)
They're really simple sentences.
In a way, it's a sequence of words.
It looked like a young kid's journal even to me.
But...
my cousins know how I feel toward them.
I guess that's why they cried with me.
(That must be why they cried with me.)
I'm not going to cry.
You must've had a cherished childhood.
I'm really grateful.
I mean, Gun Ho...
has a girlfriend.
I'm crying out of happiness.
(Crying their eyes out together out of happiness)
My thoughts and the things I want to do...
They're all made thanks to the experiences...
- and memories we made together. - That's right.
My cousins...
take up the greater part of my life.
(My cousins who take up the greater part of my life)
I love you guys.
- Thank you. - I love you guys.
- Goodness, how heartwarming. - So...
Actually, I got Jung Ho a gift.
(Another green box appears.)
"Another green box appears."
(Choked up)
Jung Ho, it's the same color.
(The eldest finally burst into tears.)
Wait a minute.
I barely held on, but I can't anymore.
He's the happiest now.
So, I sincerely...
Dae Ho is really thoughtful.
- I'm really grateful for you. - He's my brother,
but he's really thoughtful.
Jung Ho, stay healthy.
Thank you. I love you.
- How nice. This is nice. - Yes, it's really nice.
I swear that...
I will keep this...
until the day I die.
Thanks, Dae Ho.
Thank you.
(They express their heartfelt feelings through a hug.)
Gosh, that was funny.
I can't believe a day like this came.
- Gosh. - I'm envious.
- This one's color... - It's different.
- It's quite thick. - It differs in thickness.
Let me see.
Jung Ho...
- How nice. - It's pretty.
- It's pretty. - It's a wallet.
It's pretty. The inside is pretty.
(Hooray!)
- Hooray! - Like you won World Cup.
(Kim Dae Ho!)
(My champion!)
(Yes!)
- He's exhilarated. - This is really sweet.
This is the best. Jung Ho...
- You won the Grand Prize. - You're right.
This completely washed away today's fatigue.
How could you get a Bottega Veneta wallet...
when you won beef jerky earlier?
Dae Ho, thank you so much...
for creating this occasion.
Because you became successful,
our whole family, not just us, is really happy.
Dae Ho is the pride of their family.
- Their pride. - That's true.
- He's their pillar. - You're the pride of Yangpyeong,
and our family's lamp.
Your face looks so different from earlier.
(Laughing)
He's so different from when Dae Ho...
- was reading a letter. - Let me tell you this again.
- Thank you. - All right.
- Everyone. - Yes.
There's one more left.
Really? The dopamine rush never ends.
- Gae! - Gae!
- Yutnori? - Yutnori.
(Yes!)
(Gosh)
Hey, well done.
(Our Family is Always Harmonious)
- This is so nice. - Take that piece as well.
(Next story)
(Panting)
(Sighing)
(Kian84 and Dowoon are hiking in the dark?)
(Today is the day they're going to hike...)
(to welcome the New Year.)
(Dowoon, Kian84's top customer during the Grand Rainbow Bazaar)
(Happy)
(Checking their friendship as soon as they meet)
(I like hiking too.)
(Of course, I like you too.)
(You and I have the same vibe.)
(We have the same wavelength.)
(Let's go fishing together too.)
(I'd love to. Why don't we go on freshwater fishing?)
(Our happy time)
(Is this really Korea?)
(Dark path that looks like the road to the underworld)
(Why is it so high? It's not like it's the Himalayas.)
Hey! It's the peak!
(The sunrise is still far off.)
(I brought this for you.)
(Moved)
(Gosh, it's warm.)
(Cold is easier to bear when shared,)
(and their friendship deepens.)
(Warm)
(This is so funny.)
(A foil duo on top of a mountain)
(I'm happy.)
(Today's star finally appears.)
(New Year's Friendship Built with Sweat)
(Someone is running around alleys.)
(He's looking for something.)
(Actor Seo Bum June)
(He eats bread as soon as he wakes up.)
(His freezer is filled with bread.)
(Gosh, he really loves bread.)
(I thought I was looking at my freezer.)
(Today,)
(he came hunting for bread outside?)
(I'm on a bakery hopping tour.)
(Laughing)
(For his loved ones,)
(he came bakery hopping as soon as it opened.)
(Two kouign-amanns)
(Dubai croissant, pistachio toast, butter pastry, pain suisse,)
(Paris-brest, apple pie, blue cheese baguette, salt bread,)
(strawberry cream croissant, jalapeno ciabatta...)
(Where did he go with the precious bread?)
(Knocking)
(The reason he went on a bakery hopping tour)
Hello, Ji Tae.
(Actor Yoo Ji Tae)
(So, this is...)
(His heart he prepared from early morning)
(He gets to try the precious bread thanks to Bum June.)
(Even from 10 years ago and now...)
(Someone who still inspires me to dream)
(You can come to me whenever.)
(I can't forget the precious feelings and words...)
(he shared with me.)
(My Sweet Pilgrimage)